Guide to the Stanford University Slide Collection PC0141
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University slide collection
circa 1898-1980s
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University
PC0141
10.75 Linear Feet (23 boxes)
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Universities and colleges -- Buildings.; Athletics; School buildings -- California -- Design and construction.; Stanford University -- Buildings.; Stanford University -- History.; Student life.; Stanford University
- Slides
  - Stanford family (Box 1)
  - Stanford family (Box 2)
  - Students and Student life (including athletics) (Box 3)
  - Students and Student life (including athletics) (Box 4)
  - Students and Student life (including athletics) (Box 5)
  - Students and Student life (including athletics) (Box 6)
  - People (faculty and staff) (Box 7)
  - People (faculty and staff) (Box 8)
  - Places (buildings and areas) (Box 9)
  - Places (buildings and areas) (Box 10)
  - Places (buildings and areas) (Box 11)
  - Places (buildings and areas) (Box 12)
  - Events (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
  - Palo Alto and Stanford University, 1954 Jun; Accession ARCH-2001-119 (Box 15)
  - miscellaneous, Accession ARCH-2008-170 (Box 15)
  - Slides by Ken Beer and Michael Topolovac (Stanford A Place in History) 1990, Accession ARCH-2007-228 (Box 15)
  - campus views from top of Hoover Tower, June 1953; Accession ARCH-2003-312 (Box 15)
  - Stanford, Accession ARCH-1988-082 (Box 15)
  - Eric Hutchinson and others, taken by Karen Bartholomew, 1988 (Box 15)
  - moving Grove House, 1974; Accession ARCH-1989-226 (Box 15)
  - Anti-apartheid/divestment demonstration; taken by Margo Davis, 1985; Accession ARCH-1989-249 (Box 15)
  - Storey House reconstruction, 1982; Accession ARCH-1990-129 (Box 15)
  - miscellaneous SU images, Accession ARCH-2000-308 (Box 15)
  - Talk on Steinbeck (Box 15)
  - The Lyman Years, circa 1916-1943 (Box 16)
    Scope and Contents
    B/W slides of various events during President Ray Lyman's tenure.
  - Stanford slides, circa 1930s - 1990s; Multilple colored, metallic slides of various activities in Stanford (Box 17)
  - Stanford Family History Art Lecture, Accession ARCH-2014-054 (Box 18)
    Slides include images of the Stanford family, Stanford San Francisco and Palo Alto Stock Farm homes, Stanford campus scenes, railroad construction, and scenes of various European cities.
- Additional Slides, Accession ARCH-1994-022
  - Slides of Stanford, from Quads and archives for class reunion, 1890s-1930s (Box 1)
- Additional Slides, Accession ARCH-2016-054
  - ASSU Centennial Commission, 1986 (Box 1, Folders 1-2)
- Additional Slides, Accession ARCH-2017-006
  - Campus scenes, undated (Box 1)
- Additional Slides, Accession ARCH-2017-113
  Includes images of campus buildings, students, and Big Game/Axe.
  - Campus scenes, 1971-1974 (Box 1)
- Additional Slides, circa 1950s; Accession ARCH-2017-114
  - Campus scenes (Box 1)
    Includes images of Lake Lagunita, foothills, students, football games, and campus buildings.